<!--
  ~
  ~   Copyright 2020. Explore in HMS. All rights reserved.
  ~
  ~   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~   You may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~   You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~   limitations under the License.
  ~
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="introduction_text_gameservices">With HUAWEI Game Service, you will have access to a range of development capabilities, to help you develop your games more efficiently:\n\n\u2022 HUAWEI ID sign-in\n\u2022 Game addiction prevention\n\u2022 Floating window\n\u2022 Achievements\n\u2022 Events\n\u2022 Leaderboards\n\u2022 Saved games\n\u2022 Player statistics\n\u2022 Access to basic game information</string>
    <string name="whatcanyoudo_text_gameservices">\u2022 Promote your game quickly and efficiently to Huawei\'s vast base of users around the globe by letting them sign in using their HUAWEI ID. Game sign-in uses the sign-in authorization capability provided by HUAWEI Account Kit. Therefore, countries/regions supported by Game Service are the same as those supported by Account Kit.\n\u2022 Implement features like achievements and events faster, so you can quickly build the foundations for your game.\n\u2022 Perform in-depth operations tailored to your game content and your users.</string>


    <string name="info_playerstatistics_gameservices">The player statistics APIs allow you to obtain various statistics about the current player from Huawei game server so that you can learn about players\' playing habits, game progress, and payment capabilities to tailor game experiences for different players accordingly. For example, you can encourage a player who has not signed in for a long time to re-engage with your game by means such as offering an attractive reward.</string>
    <string name="info_events_gameservices">The events feature allows you to collect specific data generated by your players during gameplay and store them on Huawei game server for AppGallery Connect to use as feedback to conduct game analytics. You can flexibly define what event data your game should submit, for example, players have paid a specific amount, players reach a certain level, or players enter a specific game scene. You can also adjust your game based on submitted event data. For example, if the buyers of a specific item are much fewer than expected, you can adjust the item price and make the item more appealing to players.</string>

    <string name="event_id_gameservices">Event Id: %1$s</string>
    <string name="event_name_gameservices">Event Name: %1$s</string>
    <string name="event_value_gameservices">Event Value: %1$s</string>


    <string name="info_gte_computergraphics">HUAWEI GameTurbo Engine allows a game app to closely collaborate with the operating system for improved gameplay experience even with restricted system resources. Specifically, the app provides elaborative game scene, configuration, and network information for the system to dynamically adjust resource allocation, and the system provides its status information for the app to dynamically adjust the game load.</string>
    <string name="isgameregistered_gte_computer">Is game registered: %1$s</string>
    <string name="phone_info_gameservices">Phone info: %1$s</string>


    <string name="floatingwindow_gameservices">HUAWEI Game Suite must be integrated into games that are released in countries/regions including the Chinese mainland. HUAWEI Game Suite, displayed as a floating window, is an entry to HUAWEI GameCenter. Users can touch the window to view the value-added functions of HUAWEI GameCenter, such as browsing forums, obtaining gift packages, viewing strategies, and recording videos.</string>
    <string name="fw_precautions_gameservices">If you cannot see anything after clicking Show Floating Window, means this function is not supported in your country. If you face 7006 from BuoyClient, means that function is not supported in your country.</string>


    <string name="addiction_prevention_info_gameservices">Huawei provides a game addiction prevention solution in accordance with the Notice on Preventing Addiction Among Minors in Online Games issued by the State Administration of Press and Publication. Developers shall develop the game addiction prevention function according to the notice and app implementation logic.</string>
    <string name="trial_mode_gameservices">According to relevant rules published by China\'s State Administration of Press and Publication, an online game can provide a trial of up to one hour for guest players. In the guest mode, a player does not need to perform identity verification, but cannot top up their account or make payments. A device can have another trial at least 15 days after the last trial.</string>
    <string name="game_addiction_prevention_gameservices">When a player signs in to your game or switches your game from the background to the foreground, the game needs to report a game entering event. When a player exits your game or switches the game from the foreground to the background, the game needs to report a player exit event. HUAWEI Game Service calculates the played time of a player based on reported events. Games can query whether a player is an adult and the daily accumulated played time of the player from HUAWEI Game Service as references for performing game addiction prevention.</string>
    <string name="more_information_game_addiction_gameservices"><u>Click here to get more information about Game Addiction Prevention.</u></string>
    <string name="more_information_game_addiction_link_gameservices">https://developer.huawei.com/consumer/en/doc/development/HMSCore-Guides/game-anti-indulgence-0000001050123479</string>


    <string name="time_gameservices">Time: %1$s sn</string>
    <string name="score_gameservices">Score: %1$d point</string>


    <string name="score_gameservices_dialog">Score: %1$s point</string>
    <string name="show_floating_window">Show floating window</string>
    <string name="hide_floating_window">Hide floating window</string>
    <string name="event_samples">Event samples:</string>
    <string name="average_session_length">Average Session Length:</string>
    <string name="day_since_last_played">Day since last played:</string>
    <string name="number_of_purchases">Number of purchases:</string>
    <string name="number_of_sessions">Number of sessions:</string>
    <string name="total_purchases_amount_range">Total purchases amount range:</string>
    <string name="describe_contents">Describe contents:</string>
    <string name="phone_info">Phone Info</string>
    <string name="game_register">Game Register</string>
    <string name="result">Result</string>
    <string name="time">Time:</string>
    <string name="score">Score:</string>
    <string name="game_paused">Game paused</string>
    <string name="give_me_time">Give me time!</string>
    <string name="achievements">Achievements</string>
    <string name="leaderboards">Leaderboards</string>
    <string name="pause">pause</string>
    <string name="start">start</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="service_introduction">Service Introduction</string>
    <string name="trial_mode">Trial Mode</string>
    <string name="game_addiction_prevention">Game Addiction Prevention</string>
    <string name="game_service_sample_game">Game Service Sample Game</string>
    <string name="related_services">Related services</string>
    <string name="player_statistics">Player Statistics</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="floating_window">Floating Window</string>
    <string name="game_turbo_engine">Game Turbo Engine</string>
    <string name="addiction_prevention">Addiction Prevention</string>
    <string name="load">Load</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="load_games">Load Games</string>
    <string name="click_item_to_load_game">Click item to load game.</string>
    <string name="slide_the_item_to_be_deleted">Slide the item to be deleted.</string>
    <string name="info_image">info image</string>
    <string name="what_can_you_do_with_huawei_game_service">What Can You Do with HUAWEI Game Service?</string>
    <string name="let_s_start_please_signin_first">Let\'s start. Please sign in first.</string>
    <string name="click_to_sign_in">Click to Sign in</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="set_title_for_your_save">Set title for your save</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="give_me_time_info">You will have 10 seconds more when clicking Give me time!</string>
    <string name="slower_info">Virus will slow when clicking Make it slower!</string>
    <string name="make_it_slower">Make it slower!</string>
    <string name="url_txt_gameservice">https://developer.huawei.com/consumer/en/doc/development/HMSCore-Guides/introduction-0000001050121216</string>

</resources>