<!--
  ~
  ~   Copyright 2020. Explore in HMS. All rights reserved.
  ~
  ~   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~   You may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~   You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~   limitations under the License.
  ~
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="you_should_not_be_seeing_this_if_you_are_seeing_this_there_is_a_grave_error_occurred">YOU SHOULD NOT BE SEEING THIS! IF YOU ARE SEEING THIS, THERE IS A GRAVE ERROR OCCURRED.</string>
    <string name="desc_default_string">Wallet Kit</string>
    <string name="header_transit_passes">Transit Passes</string>
    <string name="header_smart_locks">Smart Locks for Hotels and Homes</string>
    <string name="header_movie_tickets">Movie Tickets</string>
    <string name="header_loyalty_card">Loyalty Cards</string>
    <string name="header_gift_cards">Gift Cards</string>
    <string name="header_coupons">Coupons</string>
    <string name="header_event_tickets">Event Tickets</string>
    <string name="header_boarding_passes">Boarding Passes</string>
    <string name="header_car_keys">Car Keys</string>
    <string name="header_access_cards">Access Cards</string>
    <string name="header_all_in_one_cards">All-in-One Cards</string>
    <string name="explanation">Explanation</string>
    <string name="desc_loyalty_cards">Users can add various types of loyalty cards to HUAWEI Wallet, view their exclusive benefits such as bonus points and levels anytime, and enjoy a wide range of offers such as discounts for services or products.</string>
    <string name="desc_gift_cards">Gift cards are prepaid cards that can be used only at specified stores and in specified periods such as gift cards issued by shopping malls and supermarkets. \n\nA user can purchase a gift card with a specified face value and show the payment code corresponding to the gift card for payment.\n</string>
    <string name="desc_coupons">Coupons are issued and distributed to users, providing a financial discount or rebate to promote sales.</string>
    <string name="desc_event_tickets">Event tickets refer to the electronic tickets for admission to specific events such as sports games and concerts so that users can quickly check in using their phones, improving the event operations efficiency and customer satisfaction.\n\nA user can save event tickets to HUAWEI Wallet for convenient view and real-time reminders. \n\nIn order to display a ticket, the user can simply double-press the power button or directly access it from HUAWEI Assistant, without needing to open the Wallet app. \n\nFor an NFC-enabled ticket, the user only needs to place their phones near the corresponding NFC sensor, which works even when the phone screen is locked.</string>
    <string name="desc_boarding_passes">Boarding passes are electronic credentials generated after users purchase air tickets.\n\nA user can add boarding passes to keep informed of instant flight updates. \n\nAlso users can save boarding passes to HUAWEI Wallet, for timely flight status updates and reminders.</string>
    <string name="desc_movie_tickets">Movie tickets refer to the electronic credentials for watching movies at a movie theater.\n\nA user can add movie tickets to HUAWEI Wallet so that they can receive notifications before a movie starts and check in using their phone.</string>
    <string name="desc_transit_passes">Transit passes refer to the electronic credentials added to HUAWEI Wallet after users purchase corresponding tickets.\n\nUsers can view the passes in HUAWEI Wallet anytime.</string>
    <string name="desc_access_cards">Access Card function enables users to copy access card information to the chips in their Huawei phones and then gain entrance by using their phones.\n\nAfter applying for the Wallet Kit service on HUAWEI Developers, configure the promotion service. HUAWEI Developers will deliver your product content to the content display area in HUAWEI Wallet. \n\nWhen a user taps your product, HUAWEI Wallet can read the NFC pass information of a physical access card and write the information to the chip in the user phone. At the same time, HUAWEI Wallet delivers the pass to the user and emulates the pass after the NFC pass information is completely written.\n</string>
    <string name="desc_all_in_one_card">A mobile phone can function as an all-in-one pass with "chip-device-cloud" technologies of HUAWEI, which is more convenient and secure than physical cards. The NFC technology can be used to achieve smart cards. \n\nThis is an access control solution provided for company employees. Users can add their admission credentials such as employee ID cards to HUAWEI Wallet and use their phones to enter or exit their workplaces. \n\nAll-in-one cards can guarantee security based on the integrated chip-device-cloud capabilities of Huawei phones.\n</string>
    <string name="desc_car_keys">A user can use their NFC-enabled phone to unlock their car, instead of using a physical key. A car key can be shared with others, such as family members. It will not be long before this technology is widely applied in the automotive industry of the Chinese mainland. \n\nWallet Kit provides the digital car key capability to simulate physical car keys based on "chip-device-cloud" technologies of HUAWEI. \n\nSuch digital car keys are more secure and meet the Intelligent Car Connectivity Industry Ecosystem Alliance (ICCE) standards. \n\nCurrently, this mode is available only in the Chinese mainland.\n</string>
    <string name="desc_smart_locks">This function is launched by HUAWEI Wallet together with hotels and lock vendors for users to emulate key cards onto their phones. During hotel check-in, users can add a key pass to their NFC-enabled phone and then will be able to swipe the phone to access their room. For a home key pass, a user also needs to pair the key pass with a specified door lock. \n\nHUAWEI Wallet Kit enables your users to emulate key cards of hotel and home door locks into the HUAWEI Wallet app. After applying for the Wallet Kit service on HUAWEI Developers, configure the promotion service. HUAWEI Developers will deliver your product content to the content display area in HUAWEI Wallet. When a user taps your product, HUAWEI Wallet delivers and displays an unpaired or unauthorized key pass to the user. When the user taps the pair or authorize button and moves their phone to a specified pass writer, the pass writer writes personal data into HUAWEI Wallet and completes pairing or authorization. Then, the key pass is ready for use. \n\nCurrently, this mode is available only in the Chinese mainland.\n</string>

    <string name="link_walletkit_documentation_introduction">https://developer.huawei.com/consumer/en/doc/development/HMSCore-Guides/service-introduction-0000001050042318</string>

    <string name="walletkit_explanation1">Wallet Kit is an open capability that integrates full-stack "chip-device-cloud" technologies in Huawei to provide digital passes such as cards (including ID cards), coupons, tickets and keys on an integrated platform. It enables users to add their tickets, boarding passes, loyalty cards, coupons, gift cards, and other cards or passes on their mobile phones for convenient, anytime use. It also facilitates interactions between apps and users through location-based notifications, real-time status updates, and NFC capabilities.\n\n</string>
    <string name="walletkit_explanation2">\u2022Numerous methods for adding a pass to HUAWEI Wallet via a single tap, for example, by web page, email, SMS message, HUAWEI Wallet CardStore, quick app, and app. \n\u2022Four-step integration process (registration, identity verification, service configuration, and app development), minimizing development workload and accelerating the service rollout. \n\u2022Accurate, real-time user notifications based on the time, location, Wi-Fi network, and presence of nearby services. \n\u2022Diverse methods of access, for example, via fingerprint, double-press on the power button, home screen icon, app icon, or screen-off swiping, and support for protocol- and location-based AI Selected functionality. \n\u2022Can be used in 200 + countries and regions. \n\n</string>
    <string name="walletkit_explanation3">For development details, you can use the links below to access to the official documentation of Wallet Kit. \n\nAlso you can slide right to see some features in detail.</string>
    <string name="references">1) https://developer.huawei.com/consumer/en/hms/huawei-walletkit \n\n2) https://developer.huawei.com/consumer/en/doc/development/HMSCore-Guides/service-introduction-0000001050042318"</string>
</resources>