<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--
  ~  Copyright (c) Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. 2020-2022. All rights reserved.
  ~
  ~  Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~  you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~  You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~  http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~  distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~  WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~  See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~  limitations under the License.
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="desc">
        Sign in to AppGallery Connect and click App analytics.
        Click an app, go to the Distribution analysis page, and choose Finance report.
    </string>

    <string name="desc2">
        By accessing the menus under Finance report, you can check the global
        financial data of your app, including
        the revenue, purchaser statistics, conversion rate, and subscription.
    </string>

    <string name="desc3">
        &#8226;  View data by currency (CNY, USD, or EUR)\n\n
        &#8226;  View the total revenue, Average Revenue Per Paying User (ARPPU) of the past 30 days, and average value per transaction for your app.\n\n
        &#8226;  View revenue data of last day, last 7 days, or later 30 days.\n\n
        &#8226;  On the Buyers list, you can view buyer data of the last day, last 7 days, or later 30 days.
    </string>

    <string name="desc4">
        &#8226;  View data by one or more countries/regions, currency(CNY, USD, or EUR),or time period (last day, last 7 days, last 30 days, or all time).\n\n
        &#8226;  View transaction data of the top 10 products in your app on the Revenue(by product) list, including the revenue, number of orders, refund, partial refund, and estimated annual revenue\n\n
        &#8226;  View the revenue trend curve of the app in the last seven days on the revenue trend chart.\n\n
        &#8226;  View statistics on the events that users obtain preferences at the bottom of the page, including Free products and Coupons.
    </string>

    <string name="title">
        The page provides buyer and ARPPU data.
    </string>

    <string name="desc6">
        &#8226;  View data by one or more countries/regions or time period (last day, last 7 days, last 30 days, or all time).\n\n
        &#8226;  View the statistics of all buyers, new buyers, and returning buyers in the last day, last seven days, and last 30 days. The All tab page also displays accumulated data.\n\n
        &#8226;  View the user quantity and MoM growth rate of the top 10 products in your app on the Buyers statistics by product tab page.
    </string>

    <string name="desc9">
        &#8226;  View data by one or more countries/regions or currency (CNY, USD, or EUR).\n\n
        &#8226;  View the average number of times that a user pays and average payment amount of a user in your app in each month on the Payment conversion rate list.
    </string>

    <string name="desc10">
        &#8226;  View data by one or more countries/regions, currency (CNY, USD, or EUR), or time period (last day, last 7 days, last 30 days, or all time).\n\n
        &#8226;  View the operation data of the top 10 subscription items in an app from the Subscription report list.\n\n
        &#8226;  View the trend of the total number of subscriptions of the app in the last seven days.\n\n
        &#8226;  View the total subscription revenue trend of the app in the last seven days.\n\n
        &#8226;  View order quantities of the top 3 subscription items.\n\n
        &#8226;  View statistics of new subscription sources of this month, including subscription items and the percentage of new subscriptions in the current month.

    </string>
    <string name="notification_desc_more">The Notification details report provides the statistical graphs and details of major indicators such as Sent times, Delivered times, Tapped times, and Undelivered notification details, and supports report download.</string>
    <string name="notification_desc">Sign in to AppGallery Connect and click App analytics. Click an app, go to the Operation analysis page, and choose Notification details.</string>
    <string name="notification_details">Notification Details</string>
    <string name="user_detail_desc_more">This report provides the statistical graphs and details of major indicators such as Daily active users, Daily new users, Monthly active users, and Total users, and supports report download.</string>
    <string name="user_details_desc">Sign in to AppGallery Connect and click App analytics. Click an app, go to the Operation Analysis page, and select the User details report.</string>
    <string name="user_details">User Details</string>
    <string name="arppu_title">On the ARPPU tab page, you can:</string>
    <string name="conversion_title">On the Conversion rate tab page, you can:</string>
    <string name="conversion_headline">The Conversion page provides conversion rate and ARPPU data.</string>
    <string name="revenue_title">On the Revenue page, you can:</string>
    <string name="viewing_financial_reports">Viewing Financial Reports</string>
    <string name="on_the_overview_page_you_can">On the Overview page, you can:</string>
    <string name="on_the_buyer_tab_page_you_can">On the Buyer tab page, you can:</string>
    <string name="on_the_arppu_tab_page_you_can">On the ARPPU tab page, you can:</string>
    <string name="on_the_subscription_page_you_can">On the Subscription page, you can:</string>

    <string name="url_distranalys">https://developer.huawei.com/consumer/en/doc/app/agc-help-interface-overview-0000001146438655</string>

</resources>