<!--
  ~
  ~   Copyright 2020. Explore in HMS. All rights reserved.
  ~
  ~   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~   You may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~   You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~   limitations under the License.
  ~
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="you_should_not_be_seeing_this_if_you_are_seeing_this_there_is_a_grave_error_occurred">YOU SHOULD NOT BE SEEING THIS! IF YOU ARE SEEING THIS, THERE IS A GRAVE ERROR OCCURRED.</string>
    <string name="desc_default_string">Paid Apps</string>
    <string name="desc_service_introduction">Paid Apps Introduction</string>
    <string name="header_authenticating_a_paid_app_purchase">Authenticating a Paid App Purchase</string>
    <string name="header_app_gallery_drm_service_lite_sdk">AppGallery DRM Service Lite SDK</string>

    <string name="explanation">Explanation</string>

    <string name="desc_authenticating_a_paid_app_purchase">When a user uses your paid app, you need to check whether the user has purchased the app. Please note that the AppGallery DRM Service SDK applies only to HUAWEI AppGallery 7.2.1 and later versions.\n\n As an example of an use case, company A develops a paid app, and user B purchases the app. When user B launches the app, the app checks whether user B has successfully purchased the app. If so, user B can continue using the app. Otherwise, user B is prompted to purchase the app.\n</string>
    <string name="desc_app_gallery_drm_service_lite_sdk">In order to enable customization of the AppGallery DRM Service SDK, Huawei releases the open-source AppGallery DRM Service SDK of the Lite version. Please note that the open-source Lite SDK does not support payment authentication for AppTouch and HUAWEI GameCenter, but only for HUAWEI AppGallery.\n\n\u2022If you want to customize the payment authentication mechanism, you can perform secondary development on the Lite version.\n\n\u2022If you do not have this requirement, you can directly integrate the AppGallery DRM Service SDK into your app.</string>

    <string name="docs">Docs</string>

    <string name="link_developer_paid_apps">https://developer.huawei.com/consumer/en/doc/development/AppGallery-connect-Guides/appgallerykit-paydownload-introduction</string>

    <string name="paid_apps_explanation1">AppGallery Connect enables consumers to download high-quality apps and pay through a variety of payment methods, providing a better way for you to monetize your apps. To make your app a paid one, you can set Payment type to Paid when releasing your app in AppGallery Connect. You can integrate the AppGallery DRM Service SDK to check whether a user has successfully purchased your paid app based on your needs.\n\n</string>
    <string name="paid_apps_explanation2">If you choose not to integrate the AppGallery DRM Service SDK, you do not need to perform operations in this document and only need to set your app as a paid app when configuring payment information. \n\n</string>
    <string name="paid_apps_explanation3">If you choose to integrate the AppGallery DRM Service SDK,  when a user opens your paid app, the AppGallery DRM Service SDK checks whether the user has purchased the app. If the user has not purchased the app, the SDK prompts the user to purchase it.\n\n</string>
    <string name="paid_apps_explanation4">For further details, you can use the link below to access to the official documentation of Paid Apps. \n\nAlso you can slide right to see some features in detail.</string>
</resources>