<!--
  ~  Copyright (c) Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd. 2020-2022. All rights reserved.
  ~
  ~  Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~  you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~  You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~  http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~  Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~  distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~  WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~  See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~  limitations under the License.
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="you_should_not_be_seeing_this_if_you_are_seeing_this_there_is_a_grave_error_occurred">YOU SHOULD NOT BE SEEING THIS! IF YOU ARE SEEING THIS, THERE IS A GRAVE ERROR OCCURRED.</string>
    <string name="desc_default_string">CaaS Engine</string>
    <string name="header_voice_and_video">Voice and Video Calling with Virtualized Devices</string>
    <string name="header_screen_sharing">Screen Sharing</string>
    <string name="header_in_app_calling">In-app Calling</string>
    <string name="header_custom_calls">Coming Soon - Custom Calls</string>
    <string name="desc_voice_and_video">CaaS Engine provides open APIs that are based on the HUAWEI MeeTime service. It allows app and hardware developers to easily incorporate video calling into their apps, and directly tailor the video source to their preferences with the help of HUAWEI DeviceVirtualization service.\n\n\u2022CaaS Engine provides seamless communication and connectivity between third-party devices and Huawei devices.\n\u2022By integrating CaaS Engine, developers can harness the newest communications capabilities available on Huawei devices to drive innovation.\n</string>
    <string name="desc_in_app_calling">CaaS Engine provides open APIs based on the MeeTime service, and helps app and hardware developers quickly implement real-time content sharing within their apps.\n\nCaaS Engine can be used for screen sharing scenarios by helping users share app content in real time.\n</string>
    <string name="desc_screen_sharing">CaaS Engine provides open APIs that are based on the HUAWEI MeeTime service. It enables app developers to incorporate voice and video calling into their apps social framework such as contacts and friends with ease.\n\nCaaS Engine can be used for both voice and video calls. By integrating CaaS Engine, app developers can harness the newest communications capabilities available on Huawei devices to drive innovation.\n</string>
    <string name="desc_custom_calls">HUAWEI CaaS Kit-Custom Call provides open APIs based on the MeeTime service, and helps developers quickly implement voice and video call services directly from social framework (such as contacts and friends) within their app.\n\nDevelopers can customize the text displayed on the incoming and outgoing call screens, to enhance user experience for calls made to strangers, and safeguard user privacy by hiding the real mobile numbers of both parties from view.\n</string>
    <string name="explanation">Explanation</string>

    <string name="link_walletkit_documentation_introduction">https://developer.huawei.com/consumer/en/doc/development/connectivity-Guides/virtualized-devices-calling-introduction-0000001051089010</string>

    <string name="caas_engine__explanation1">HUAWEI CaaS Engine provides app and hardware developers access to open abilities based on the HUAWEI MeeTime service. This engine makes video calling achievable for Huawei phones as well as a variety of apps and partnered smart devices, building a giant real-time communication network for the ultimate user experience.\n\n</string>
    <string name="caas_engine__explanation2">\u2022With HD image quality and ultra-low bandwidth provides higher image quality with lower bandwidth requirements. \n\u2022By smooth calls and even with weak network signals delivers clear visuals and a smooth video stream in real time, even when the signal is poor. \n\u2022Intelligently detects the bandwidth then uses seamless software and hardware collaboration to maintain a stable call. \n</string>
    <string name="caas_engine__explanation3">For development details, you can use the links below to access to the official documentation of CaaS Engine. \n\nAlso you can slide right to see some features in detail.</string>
    <string name="references">1) https://developer.huawei.com/consumer/en/caas-kit \n\n2) https://developer.huawei.com/consumer/en/doc/development/connectivity-Guides/virtualized-devices-calling-introduction-0000001051089010"</string>
</resources>