<!--
  ~
  ~   Copyright 2020. Explore in HMS. All rights reserved.
  ~
  ~   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~   You may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~   You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~   limitations under the License.
  ~
  -->

<resources>
    <string name="title_ab_test">A/B Testing</string>
    <string name="txt_abtest">A/B Testing provides a collection of refined operation tools to optimize app experience and improve key conversion and growth indicators. You can use the service to create one or more A/B tests engaging different user groups to compare your variants of app UI design, copywriting, product functions, or marketing activities for performance metrics and find the best one that meets user requirements. This helps you make correct decisions. A/B Testing is commonly used by large Internet companies, with hundreds of A/B tests conducted every week.</string>
    <string name="txt_main_func">A/B Testing can help you when you:\nCannot decide which variant to choose for the optimal effect.\nWorry that great updates of your app may not get positive feedback from users.</string>
    <string name="txt_new_ui_design">New UI Design Testing</string>
    <string name="txt_new_ui_design_exp">When you have multiple UI design plans for the same scenario, you can create a remote configuration experiment in A/B Testing to deliver these variants to users for responsiveness. For example, the following two figures are variants for the home page design of the Huawei Health app. The A/B test result shows that more users launch the app with the home page A, and operations personnel therefore then release variant A to all users. Similarly, A/B testing also applies to icon design in apps.</string>
    <string name="txt_app_copyright">App Copywriting Testing</string>
    <string name="txt_app_copyright_exp">Operations personnel can push notifications to engage users or wake up inactive users. The push effect significantly lies on whether the notification copywriting is attractive enough. A/B Testing can help evaluate your variants. For example, the following two figures are variants for the update notification of the HUAWEI Video app. The A/B test result shows that variant A gets more taps, and operations personnel then release variant A to all users. A/B Testing also applies to other types of copywriting.</string>
    <string name="txt_app_function">App Function Testing</string>
    <string name="txt_app_function_exp">Function updates are common for an app. A/B Testing can help you distribute your function updates to some users for responsiveness and feedback, which can be used as a reference for you to determine whether to officially release the updates to all users. For example, the following two figures show the update of the Free area in the HUAWEI AppGallery app.</string>
    <string name="txt__link">https://developer.huawei.com/consumer/en/agconnect/abtest-introduction/</string>
</resources>